Guide to the Sarenco Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Sarenco papers
1957-2012
GEN MSS 971
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
22.25
(25 boxes) + 40 broadside
The collection consists of correspondence, typewriter poems, photographs, artwork, artist books, and photocopy books documenting the work of Sarenco. Notable correspondents inlcude Dēmosthenēs Agraphiōtēs, Gianni Bertini, Julien Blaine, Jean-François Bory, Ugo Carrega, Henri Chopin, Pierre Garnier, Ladislav Novák, and Lamberto Pignotti. Typewriter poems include works by Dēmosthenēs Agraphiōtēs, Bartolomé Ferrando, Henri Chopin, Hans Clavin, Ilse Garnier, Pierre Garnier, Arrigo Lora-Totino, Ladislav Novák, Seiichi Niikuni, and Sarenco. Photographs include images of Julien Blaine, Jean-François Bory, Ugo Carrega, Hans Clavin, Ladislav Novák, Lamberto Pignotti, Sarenco, and others. Artwork, artist books, and photocopy books include works by Dēmosthenēs Agraphiōtēs, Julien Blaine, Ugo Carrega, Ladislav Novák, Sarenco, and others.
Sarenco, 1945-
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Box 65 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Sarenco
Sarenco (Isaia Mabellini, born 1945) is an Italian poet who was active as the leader of a radical group of visual poets based in Florence in the 1970s. Sarenco edited Lotta poetica (Poetic Struggle), a communist, anti-imperialist, anti-capitalist periodical devoted primarily to poetry with visual elements.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Sarenco on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2013.
Arrangement
Organzied into five series: I. Correspondence, 1964-2012. II. Typewriter Poems, 1957-2006. III. Photographs, circa 1960s-2000s. IV. Artwork, 1960-2012. V. Artist and photocopy books, 1971-2012.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of correspondence, typewriter poems, photographs, artwork, artist books, and photocopy books documenting the work of Sarenco. Notable correspondents inlcude Dēmosthenēs Agraphiōtēs, Gianni Bertini, Julien Blaine, Jean-François Bory, Ugo Carrega, Henri Chopin, Pierre Garnier, Ladislav Novák, and Lamberto Pignotti. Typewriter poems include works by Dēmosthenēs Agraphiōtēs, Bartolomé Ferrando, Henri Chopin, Hans Clavin, Ilse Garnier, Pierre Garnier, Arrigo Lora-Totino, Ladislav Novák, Seiichi Niikuni, and Sarenco. Photographs include images of Julien Blaine, Jean-François Bory, Ugo Carrega, Hans Clavin, Ladislav Novák, Lamberto Pignotti, Sarenco, and others. Artwork, artist books, and photocopy books include works by Dēmosthenēs Agraphiōtēs, Julien Blaine, Ugo Carrega, Ladislav Novák, Sarenco, and others.
Poets, Italian -- 20th Century -- Archives; Visual poetry, Italian -- 20th Century; Born digital; Photographs -- Italy -- 20th Century; Visual poetry; Poets -- Italy -- 20th Century; Agraphiōtēs, Dēmosthenēs, 1946-; Bertini, Gianni, 1922-2010; Blaine, Julien, 1942-; Bory, Jean-François, 1938-; Carrega, Ugo, 1935-2014; Chopin, Henri, 1922-2008; Clavin, Hans; Ferrando, Bartolomé, 1951-; Garnier, Ilse; Garnier, Pierre, 1928-2014; Lora-Totino, Arrigo, 1928-; Niikuni, Seiichi, 1925-1977; Novák, Ladislav, 1925-1999; Pignotti, Lamberto, 1926-; Sarenco, 1945-
- Correspondence, 1964-2012; Series I
  Arrangement
  Correspondence is arranged in the order in which it was received.
  - 1-Pierre Garnier, undated (Box 1)
  - 2-Pierre Garnier, 2012 June 12 (Box 1)
  - 3-Adriano Accattino, 2012 May 17 (Box 1)
  - 4-Pierre Garnier, 2012 May 19 (Box 1)
  - 5-Pierre Garnier, 2012 May 6 (Box 1)
  - 6-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2011 November 28 (Box 1)
  - 7-Bart De Baere, undated (Box 1)
  - 8-Julien Blaine, 2010 March 1 (Box 1)
  - 9-Anna Banana, 1998 October 8 (Box 1)
  - 10-Monique Pourtalès, 1998 October 14 (Box 1)
  - 11-Pablo Echaurren, undated (Box 1)
  - 12-Karel Trinkewitz, undated (Box 1)
  - 13-Anna Banana, 1998 December 11 (Box 1)
  - 14-Josef Anton Riedl, 1998 December 5 (Box 1)
  - 15-Martino Oberto, 1998 May 4 (Box 1)
  - 16-Luca Patella, 1998 (Box 1)
  - 17-Ramon Salvo, 1998 March 16 (Box 1)
  - 18-Lamberto Pignotti, 1998 April 2 (Box 1)
  - 19-Aleksander Rojc, 1998 March 18 (Box 1)
  - 20-Bernard Pagès, 1999 July 2 (Box 1)
  - 21-Antonio Ria, 2004 July 13 (Box 1)
  - 22-Pierre Garnier, 2010 September 10 (Box 1)
  - 23-Simone Frittelli, 2010 September 17 (Box 1)
  - 24-Gian Paolo Roffi, 2010 October 12 (Box 1)
  - 25-Luigi Bonotto, undated (Box 1)
  - 26-Jean-François Bory, 2011 May 5 (Box 1)
  - 27-Ingeborg Luescher, 2010 December 19 (Box 1)
  - 28-Luc Fierens, 2010 May 9 (Box 1)
  - 29-Takahashi Shohachiro, 2010 March 15 (Box 1)
  - 30-Albrecht/d., 2010 May 29 (Box 1)
  - 31-Eva Vlasakova, undated (Box 1)
  - 32-Pierre Garnier, undated (Box 1)
  - 33-Pierre Garnier, 2009 December 20 (Box 1)
  - 34-Pierre Garnier, 2009 December 20 (Box 1)
  - 35-Pierre Garnier, 2009 December 17 (Box 1)
  - 36-Julio Campal, 1968 February 9 (Box 1)
  - 37-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 38-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 39-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 40-Michele Perfetti, 2005 October 29 (Box 1)
  - 41-Robin Greev, undated (Box 1)
  - 42-Fernando Millan, 2000 March 29 (Box 1)
  - 43-Nicholas Zurbrugg, 2000 March 25 (Box 1)
  - 44-Balint Szombathy, 2000 March 9 (Box 1)
  - 45-Valerio Dehò, undated (Box 1)
  - 46-Raul Aguirre, 1962 April 18 (Box 1)
  - 47-Carlos Sanz, undated (Box 1)
  - 48-Jochin Diez, 1969 March 29 (Box 1)
  - 49-Anonimo, 1966 April 5 (Box 1)
  - 50-Franco Verdi, 1966 April 2 (Box 1)
  - 51-Henri Chopin, 1966 March 14 (Box 1)
  - 52-W. Mark Sutherland, undated (Box 1)
  - 53-Arrigo-Lora Totino, 1998 November 5 (Box 1)
  - 54-Bill Bissett, undated (Box 1)
  - 55-Carlos Vitale, 1998 October 7 (Box 1)
  - 56-Francesco Saverio Dodaro, 1998 December 24 (Box 1)
  - 57-Stelio Maria Martini, 1998 May 4 (Box 1)
  - 58-Dimitri Bulatov, undated (Box 1)
  - 59-Giovanni Lista, undated (Box 1)
  - 60-Ingeborg Luescher, undated (Box 1)
  - 61-Reinhard Dohl, 1966 April 7 (Box 1)
  - 62-Ludwig Harig, undated (Box 1)
  - 63-André Magnin, undated (Box 1)
  - 64-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2002 April 22 (Box 1)
  - 65-Julien Blaine, 1998 November 12 (Box 1)
  - 66-Ludmila Dohalova, 1999 February 5 (Box 1)
  - 67-Pierre Garnier, 1999 January 6 (Box 1)
  - 68-Julien Blaine, 2001 November 19 (Box 1)
  - 69-Luca Patella, 1999 March 15 (Box 1)
  - 70-Julien Blaine, 2001 May 16 (Box 1)
  - 71-Martina Corgnati, undated (Box 1)
  - 72-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2002 January 10 (Box 1)
  - 73-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2002 February 2 (Box 1)
  - 74-Giorgio Di Genova, 2002 June 25 (Box 1)
  - 75-Nathalie Thibat, 1998 September 30 (Box 1)
  - 76-Fernanda Fedi, 1998 July 18 (Box 1)
  - 77-John Furnival, 1998 December 3 (Box 1)
  - 78-Julien Blaine, 1998 November 26 (Box 1)
  - 79-Monique Pourtalès, undated (Box 1)
  - 80-Francesco Saverio Dodaro, 1998 February 23 (Box 1)
  - 81-Fernanda Fedi, 1998 June 20 (Box 1)
  - 82-Valeri Scherstjanoi, undated (Box 1)
  - 83-Liliana De Matteis, 1998 January 13 (Box 1)
  - 84-W. Mark Sutherland, 1999 July 29 (Box 1)
  - 85-Eduardo Apraiz, undated (Box 1)
  - 86-Julien Blaine, 1999 (Box 1)
  - 87-Eduardo Apraiz, 1968 (Box 1)
  - 88-Héctor, 1967 (Box 1)
  - 89-David, 1968 February 19 (Box 1)
  - 90-Héctor, 1967 October 23 (Box 1)
  - 91-Antonio, 1968 March 21 (Box 1)
  - 92-Julio Campal, 1966 July 19 (Box 1)
  - 93-Carlos Sanz, 1967 May 27 (Box 1)
  - 94-Enrique Uribe, 1967 March 9 (Box 1)
  - 95-Manolo Adrada, 1967 December 27 (Box 1)
  - 96-Héctor, 1968 March 22 (Box 1)
  - 97-Julio Campal, 1966 June 17 (Box 1)
  - 98-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 99-Anonimo (per Julio Campal), undated (Box 1)
  - 100-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 101-Julio Campal, 1968 February 14 (Box 1)
  - 102-Carlos Sanz, 1967 September 27 (Box 1)
  - 103-Raul Gustavo Aguirre, 1964 April 2 (Box 1)
  - 104-Eusebio Sempere, 1966 June 13 (Box 1)
  - 105-Anonimo (per Julio Campal), 1968 February 19 (Box 1)
  - 106-Tiziana Di Franco, 2000 July 13 (Box 1)
  - 107-Antonio Ruiz, undated (Box 1)
  - 108-Aldo Tagliaferro, 2002 July 14 (Box 1)
  - 109-Pierre Garnier, 2003 August 27 (Box 1)
  - 110-Jakob De Chirico, undated (Box 1)
  - 111-Karel Trinkewitz, undated (Box 1)
  - 112-Bogdanka Poznanovic, 2001 April 8 (Box 1)
  - 113-Karel Trinkewitz, 2000 April 15 (Box 1)
  - 114-Karel Trinkewitz, undated (Box 1)
  - 115-Ladislav Novak, 1999 July 4 (Box 1)
  - 116-Enrique Uribe, undated (Box 1)
  - 117-Enrique Uribe, 1967 (Box 1)
  - 118-Enrique Uribe, 1968 February 6 (Box 1)
  - 119-Enrique Uribe, 1967 April 1 (Box 1)
  - 120-Luc Fierens, 2001 March 25 (Box 1)
  - 121-Ingeborg Luescher, 2002 May 17 (Box 1)
  - 122-Julien Blaine, 2002 February 7 (Box 1)
  - 123-Ingeborg Luescher, 2002 May 14 (Box 1)
  - 124-Tullio Catalano, undated (Box 1)
  - 125-Pepa Brossa, 1999 May 3 (Box 1)
  - 126-Tanabe Shin, undated (Box 1)
  - 127-Chema De Francisco Guinea, 1998 January (Box 1)
  - 128-Dmitry Bulatov, 1998 October 28 (Box 1)
  - 129-Gino Gini, 1999 February 24 (Box 1)
  - 130-Luc Fierens, 1998 December 28 (Box 1)
  - 131-Balint Szombathy, 1998 November 29 (Box 1)
  - 132-Julien Blaine, 1998 December 14 (Box 1)
  - 133-Sergio Cena, 2000 July 11 (Box 1)
  - 134-Ramon Salvo, 1998 February 18 (Box 1)
  - 135-Karel Trinkewitz, 1999 August 18 (Box 1)
  - 136-Pierre Garnier, 2009 May 15 (Box 1)
  - 137-Ugo Carrega, 2009 April 24 (Box 1)
  - 138-Pierre Garnier, 2009 October 7 (Box 1)
  - 139-Pierre Garnier, 2009 October (Box 1)
  - 140-Jokin Diez, 1967 February 18 (Box 1)
  - 141-Marie Lys, undated (Box 1)
  - 142-Jokin Diez, 1966 November 2 (Box 1)
  - 143-Gino Gini, 2006 February 6 (Box 1)
  - 144-Pierre Garnier, 2010 October 4 (Box 1)
  - 145-Giorgio Fogazzi, 2010 September 6 (Box 1)
  - 146-Julien Blaine, 1999 November 20 (Box 1)
  - 147-Sarmento, 2001 February 20 (Box 1)
  - 148-Karel Trinkewitz, 2001 (Box 1)
  - 149-J.M. Calleja, 2004 August 28 (Box 1)
  - 150-Irma Blank, 2004 October 15 (Box 1)
  - 151-Giorgio Fogazzi, 2004 December 11 (Box 1)
  - 152-Ana Haterly, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - 153-Mazenna Kosiniska, 1999 January 15 (Box 1)
  - 154-Luc Fierens, 2005 January 3 (Box 1)
  - 155-Ugo Carrega, undated (Box 1)
  - 156-Giovanni Fontana, 1996 June 18 (Box 1)
  - 157-Pierre Garnier, 2009 June 16 (Box 1)
  - 158-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 159-Pierre Garnier, 2009 May 19 (Box 1)
  - 160-Pierre Garnier, 2009 September 29 (Box 1)
  - 161-Francesco Saverio Dodaro, 2009 June 29 (Box 1)
  - 162-Ian Maalin, 2008 August 26 (Box 1)
  - 163-Ladislav Novak, 1986 March 17 (Box 1)
  - 164-Ladislav Novak, 1994 March 30 (Box 1)
  - 165-Ladislav Novak, 1994 May 2 (Box 1)
  - 166-Philippe Castellin, undated (Box 1)
  - 167-Ladislav Novak, 1997 October 30 (Box 1)
  - 168-Pablo Echaurren, undated (Box 1)
  - 169-Giovanni Fontana, 1999 September 3 (Box 1)
  - 170-Cesar Figuereido, undated (Box 1)
  - 171-Pierre Garnier, 2011 November 18 (Box 1)
  - 172-Pierre Garnier, 2011 December 3 (Box 1)
  - 173-Sarenco, 2009 April 16 (Box 1)
  - 174-Julio Campal, 1966 May 7 (Box 1)
  - 175-Julio Campal, 1966 June 18 (Box 1)
  - 176-Hellmut Geissner, 1966 May 31 (Box 1)
  - 177-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 178-Reimer Jochims, 1966 April 22 (Box 1)
  - 179-Bp Nichol, undated (Box 1)
  - 180-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 181-Arrigo Lora Totino, 1966 April 22 (Box 1)
  - 182-Anonimo, undated (Box 1)
  - 183-Ugo Carrega, 2009 February 20 (Box 1)
  - 184-Carl-Friederich Claus, 1966 April 12 (Box 1)
  - 185-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2002 October 30 (Box 1)
  - 186-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2002 July 3 (Box 1)
  - 187-Julien Blaine, 2002 November 26 (Box 1)
  - 188-Roberta Baj, undated (Box 1)
  - 189-Pierre Garnier, 2003 July 28 (Box 1)
  - 190-Julien Blaine, 2003 June 3 (Box 1)
  - 191-André Magnin, 2001 (Box 1)
  - 192-Nahl Nucha, 1998 March 9 (Box 1)
  - 193-Pierre Garnier, 2010 March 17 (Box 1)
  - 194-Miroslav Klivar, 1999 February 27 (Box 1)
  - 195-Jan Van Toorn, 1998 January 27 (Box 1)
  - 196-Fernando Millan, 1998 February 5 (Box 1)
  - 197-Predrag Sidjanin, 1999 October 1 (Box 1)
  - 198-Ladislav Novak, 1999 June 6 (Box 1)
  - 199-Endre Skarosi, undated (Box 1)
  - 200-Ladislav Novak, 1999 July 4 (Box 1)
  - 201-Pierre Garnier, undated (Box 1)
  - 202-Pawel Petasz, 1999 September 16 (Box 1)
  - 203-Fernando Millan, 1999 September 7 (Box 1)
  - 204-Predrag Sidjanin, 1999 September 2 (Box 1)
  - 205-Gianni Bertini, 2000 April 2 (Box 1)
  - 206-Gianni Bertini, 1998 February 18 (Box 1)
  - 207-Gianni Bertini, 2000 March 3 (Box 1)
  - 208-Gianni Bertini, 2008 July 7 (Box 1)
  - 209-Gianni Bertini, 2000 March 25 (Box 1)
  - 210-Gianni Bertini, 2000 March 25 (Box 1)
  - 211-Gianni Bertini, 2005 April 20 (Box 1)
  - 212-Gianni Bertini, 2006 December 11 (Box 1)
  - 213-Gianni Bertini, 2007 October 25 (Box 1)
  - 214-Gianni Bertini, 2000 August 23 (Box 1)
  - 215-Gianni Bertini, 2002 September 19 (Box 1)
  - 216-Gianni Bertini, 1998 January 17 (Box 1)
  - 217-Gianni Bertini, 2005 May 22 (Box 1)
  - 218-Gianni Bertini, 2002 March 25 (Box 1)
  - 219-Gianni Bertini, 2000 April 27 (Box 1)
  - 220-Gianni Bertini, 2009 November 16 (Box 1)
  - 221-Gianni Bertini, 2000 March 17 (Box 1)
  - 222-Lucia Marcucci, 2011 June 9 (Box 1)
  - 223-Jean-François Bory, 2000 March 29 (Box 1)
  - 224-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 225-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 226-Richard Martel, 1987 January 22 (Box 1)
  - 227-Ursula Mildner, 1998 March 5 (Box 1)
  - 228-Macba Barcelona, undated (Box 1)
  - 229-Jiri Machalicky, 1999 January 23 (Box 1)
  - 230-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2000 July 28 (Box 1)
  - 231-Albrecht/d., 2010 June 11 (Box 1)
  - 232-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 233-Pierre Garnier, 2011 October 31 (Box 1)
  - 234-Bernard Heidsieck, 1987 January 25 (Box 1)
  - 235-Arrigo Lora-Totino, 1978 December 17 (Box 1)
  - 236-Josef Anton Riedl, 1997 October 25 (Box 1)
  - 237-Lamberto Pignotti, 1997 November 12 (Box 1)
  - 238-Carlos Pazos, 1997 November 15 (Box 1)
  - 239-Pierre Garnier, 1994 April 2 (Box 1)
  - 240-Lamberto Pignotti, 1994 April 7 (Box 1)
  - 241-Pierre Garnier, undated (Box 1)
  - 242-Carlo Palli, 2006 June 9 (Box 1)
  - 243-Pierre Garnier, 2006 July 22 (Box 1)
  - 244-Anonimo, 1997 January 27 (Box 1)
  - 245-Roland Sabatier, 1997 November 5 (Box 1)
  - 246-John Furnival, 1997 November 12 (Box 1)
  - 247-Pierre Garnier, 1997 November 3 (Box 1)
  - 248-Josée Lapeyrère, 1997 October 26 (Box 1)
  - 249-Jean-François Bory, 2006 May 25 (Box 1)
  - 250-Julien Blaine, 2006 May 26 (Box 1)
  - 251-Ito Motoyuki, 2006 April 3 (Box 1)
  - 252-Ruth Aklander, 2006 March 17 (Box 1)
  - 253-Francesco Conz, 2006 March 21 (Box 1)
  - 254-Leonardo Rosa, 1997 March 6 (Box 1)
  - 255-Biblioteca Civica di Verona, 1997 April 4 (Box 1)
  - 256-Rosalie Marculic, 1997 (Box 1)
  - 257-Ingeborg Luescher, 2003 February 7 (Box 1)
  - 258-Aldo Tagliaferri, 1999 December 9 (Box 1)
  - 259-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2000 January 24 (Box 1)
  - 260-Julien Blaine, 2005 March 7 (Box 1)
  - 261-Julien Blaine, 2003 (Box 1)
  - 262-Julien Blaine, 2006 July 12 (Box 1)
  - 263-Giovanni Fontana, 2005 August 3 (Box 1)
  - 264-Arrigo Lora-Totino, 2005 December 15 (Box 1)
  - 265-Siegfried J. Schmidt, 2005 December 23 (Box 1)
  - 266-Tomaso Binga, undated (Box 1)
  - 267-Monty Cantsin, 2006 February 28 (Box 1)
  - 268-Pierre Garnier, 2006 March 17 (Box 1)
  - 269-Anna Oberto, 2006 March 10 (Box 1)
  - 270-Fernando Aguiar, 1994 June 19 (Box 1)
  - 271-Klaus Peter Denker, 1994 May 6 (Box 1)
  - 272-Fernando Aguiar, 1994 May 13 (Box 1)
  - 273-Lucia Marcucci, undated (Box 1)
  - 274-Takahashi Shohachiro, 1994 May 27 (Box 1)
  - 275-Alain Arias-Misson, undated (Box 1)
  - 276-Eric Andersen, 2006 February 17 (Box 1)
  - 277-Vittore Baroni, 2006 March 3 (Box 1)
  - 278-Ingeborg Luescher, undated (Box 1)
  - 279-Ingeborg Luescher, undated (Box 1)
  - 280-Tracce, 2008 (Box 1)
  - 281-Ladislav Novak, undated (Box 1)
  - 282-Julien Blaine, 2002 (Box 1)
  - 283-Julien Blaine, 1994 November 28 (Box 1)
  - 284-Julien Blaine, 1994 February 21 (Box 1)
  - 285-Julien Blaine, 1984 February 28 (Box 1)
  - 286-Julien Blaine, 1983 January 25 (Box 1)
  - 287-Alain Arias-Misson, undated (Box 1)
  - 288-Bernard Heidsieck, 1986 April 11 (Box 1)
  - 289-Alain Arias-Misson, undated (Box 1)
  - 290-Louisiana Museum, 1987 January 28 (Box 1)
  - 291-Gyorgy Galantai, 1987 November 14 (Box 1)
  - 292-Pierre Garnier, 1999 January 16 (Box 1)
  - 293-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2000 May 22 (Box 1)
  - 294-John Furnival, 1999 January 25 (Box 1)
  - 295-Pierre Garnier, 2001 July 9 (Box 1)
  - 296-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 297-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2001 April 10 (Box 1)
  - 298-Julien Blaine, 2001 June 26 (Box 1)
  - 299-PAC Milano, 2000 October 13 (Box 1)
  - 300-Giovanni Sesia, undated (Box 1)
  - 301-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 302-Rodolfo Vitone, 1997 (Box 1)
  - 303-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 304-Julien Blaine, 2002 September 30 (Box 1)
  - 305-Arrigo Lora-Totino, 1999 January 6 (Box 1)
  - 306-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2000 April 26 (Box 1)
  - 307-Giuseppe Desiato, undated (Box 1)
  - 308-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2000 (Box 1)
  - 309-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2000 (Box 1)
  - 310-Ivana Martinez Vollaro, 1999 (Box 1)
  - 311-Julien Blaine, 1999 (Box 1)
  - 312-Mario Nanni, undated (Box 1)
  - 313-Pierre Garnier, 2001 March 5 (Box 1)
  - 315-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2000 September 11 (Box 1)
  - 314-Klaus Groh, 1999 August 14 (Box 1)
  - 316-Julien Blaine, 2003 March 30 (Box 1)
  - 317-Julien Blaine, 1998 September 13 (Box 1)
  - 318-Julien Blaine, 1994 April 14 (Box 1)
  - 319-Gisèle Breteau Skira, 1994 March 3 (Box 1)
  - 320-Marvin Sackner, 1994 July 16 (Box 1)
  - 321-Luc Fierens, 2005 (Box 1)
  - 322-Fernando Aguiar, 2005 November 8 (Box 1)
  - 323-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 324-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 325-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2001 March 1 (Box 1)
  - 326-Julien Blaine, 2000 October 18 (Box 1)
  - 327-Julien Blaine, 2003 January 6 (Box 1)
  - 328-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 1998 November 9 (Box 1)
  - 329-Bartolomé Ferrando, undated (Box 1)
  - 330-Giorgio Fogazzi, undated (Box 1)
  - 331-Ingeborg Luescher, undated (Box 1)
  - 332-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2004 June 23 (Box 1)
  - 333-Antonio Ria, 2004 September 9 (Box 1)
  - 334-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 2004 June 20 (Box 1)
  - 335-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2004 July 29 (Box 1)
  - 336-Ingeborg Luescher, 2004 May 9 (Box 1)
  - 337-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2001 July 1 (Box 1)
  - 338-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 2000 August 29 (Box 1)
  - 339-Julien Blaine, 2005 October 24 (Box 1)
  - 340-Pierre Garnier, 2007 November 2 (Box 1)
  - 341-Ingeborg Luescher, 2007 October 4 (Box 1)
  - 342-BAU, 2008 December 13 (Box 1)
  - 343-Anonimo, 2005 February 22 (Box 1)
  - 344-William Xerra, 2006 January 29 (Box 1)
  - 345-Karel Adamus, 2006 March 1 (Box 1)
  - 346-Giorgio Fogazzi, 2006 March 20 (Box 1)
  - 347-Pavel Rudolf, 2006 April 10 (Box 1)
  - 348-Jan Maalin, 2006 April 1 (Box 1)
  - 349-W.Mark Sutherland, undated (Box 1)
  - 350-Alessandro Bonfanti, 2008 January 16 (Box 1)
  - 351-Mauro Dal Fior, 2006 December 17 (Box 1)
  - 352-Giorgio Fogazzi, 2006 January 30 (Box 1)
  - 353-Richard Martel, undated (Box 1)
  - 354-Gerhard Jaschke, 2006 March 5 (Box 1)
  - 355-Klaus Groh, 2005 July 5 (Box 1)
  - 356-Polana Bregantova, 2006 September 12 (Box 1)
  - 357-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 2006 July 31 (Box 1)
  - 358-Enzo Minarelli, 2005 (Box 1)
  - 359-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 2005 (Box 1)
  - 360-Giorgio Fogazzi, 2005 December 15 (Box 1)
  - 361-Anna Oberto, 2006 January 10 (Box 1)
  - 362-John Furnival, 2006 January 15 (Box 1)
  - 363-Siegfried J. Schmidt, 2005 December 5 (Box 1)
  - 364-Bartolomé Ferrando, 2000 January 20 (Box 1)
  - 365-Lamberto Pignotti, 2005 (Box 1)
  - 366-Lucia Marcucci, undated (Box 1)
  - 367-Stelio Maria Martini, 2005 May 10 (Box 1)
  - 368-Peppe Morra, 2006 June 12 (Box 1)
  - 369-Karel Adamus, 2006 March 1 (Box 1)
  - 370-Takahashi Shohachiro, 2006 June 5 (Box 1)
  - 371-John Furnival, 2006 May 2 (Box 1)
  - 372-BAU, 2007 October 29 (Box 1)
  - 373-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 2006 (Box 1)
  - 374-Fernando Andolcetti, undated (Box 1)
  - 375-BAU, 2007 December 10 (Box 1)
  - 376-M.W. Morris, 1999 October 28 (Box 1)
  - 377-Julien Blaine, 1999 December 12 (Box 1)
  - 378-Sergio Cena, 1999 December 10 (Box 1)
  - 379-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 380-Zama, 1999 October 1 (Box 1)
  - 381-Pawel Petasz, 1999 October 11 (Box 1)
  - 382-BAU, 2008 May 11 (Box 1)
  - 383-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2008 June 1 (Box 1)
  - 384-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2005 March 24 (Box 1)
  - 385-Leonardo Clerici, undated (Box 1)
  - 386-Julien Blaine, undated (Box 1)
  - 387-Antonio Ria, 2005 March 18 (Box 1)
  - 388-Luigi Stampini, undated (Box 1)
  - 389-Miroslav Klivar, 2005 June 23 (Box 1)
  - 390-John Furnival, undated (Box 1)
  - 391-Fernando Andolcetti, 2005 December 16 (Box 1)
  - 392-Bartolomé Ferrando, 2006 January 16 (Box 1)
  - 393-Pierre Garnier, 2007 May 3 (Box 1)
  - 394-Takahashi Shohachiro, 2007 (Box 1)
  - 395-John Furnival, 2007 May 9 (Box 1)
  - 396-Pierre Garnier, 2007 May 24 (Box 1)
  - 397-BAU, 2007 June 21 (Box 1)
  - 398-BAU, 2007 June 30 (Box 1)
  - 399-Ario Pizzarelli, 2007 June 9 (Box 1)
  - 400-Pierre Garnier, 2007 May 17 (Box 1)
  - 401-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 2006 July 15 (Box 1)
  - 402-BAU, 2007 May 25 (Box 1)
  - 403-Pierre Garnier, 2007 April 21 (Box 1)
  - 404-BAU, 2007 May 4 (Box 1)
  - 405-Pierre Garnier, 2007 May 14 (Box 1)
  - 407-Pierre Garnier, 2007 December 22 (Box 1)
  - 408-Jacques Donguy, 2008 March 5 (Box 1)
  - 409-Pierre Garnier, 2008 February 24 (Box 1)
  - 410-BAU, 2008 March 13 (Box 1)
  - 411-BAU, 2008 March 21 (Box 1)
  - 412-Albrecht/d., 1998 January 8 (Box 1)
  - 413-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, undated (Box 1)
  - 414-Demosthenes Agrafiotis, 2006 July 16 (Box 1)
  - 415-Gérard Fioretti, 2008 April 25 (Box 1)
  - 416-BAU, 2007 March 26 (Box 1)
  - 417-Pierre Garnier, 2007 March 24 (Box 1)
  - 418-BAU, 2007 April 6 (Box 1)
  - 419-Pierre Garnier, 2007 April 18 (Box 1)
  - 420-BAU, 2007 April 21 (Box 1)
  - 421-Julien Blaine, 2007 March 13 (Box 1)
  - 422-Eric Girard, 2005 February 15 (Box 1)
  - 423-Michele Perfetti, 2005 May 7 (Box 1)
  - 424-Miroslav Klivar, 2005 May 6 (Box 1)
  - 425-John Furnival, undated (Box 1)
  - 426-Takahashi Shohachiro, 2006 May 10 (Box 1)
  - 427-Ilse Garnier, 2002 July 4 (Box 1)
  - 428-Ugo Carrega, undated (Box 1)
  - 429-Humphrey Ottenhof, 2005 November 24 (Box 1)
  - 430-Siegfried J. Schmidt, 2007 October 6 (Box 1)
  - 431-Fernando Andolcetti, 2007 October 6 (Box 1)
  - 432-Pierre Garnier, 2007 July 14 (Box 1)
  - 433-Pierre Garnier, 2007 July 18 (Box 1)
  - 434-Fernando Andolcetti, 2007 October 12 (Box 1)
  - 435-Takahashi Shohachiro, 1994 April 11 (Box 1)
  - 436-Pierre Garnier, 1994 April 12 (Box 1)
  - 437-Rodolfo Vitone, 2004 March 25 (Box 1)
  - 438-Stelio Maria Martini, undated (Box 1)
  - 439-Bernard Heidsieck, 1994 May 12 (Box 1)
  - 440-Michele Perfetti, 1994 May 10 (Box 1)
  - 441-John Furnival, 1997 December 12 (Box 1)
  - 442-Pierre Garnier, 1991 December 10 (Box 1)
  - 443-Bernard Heisieck, 1993 September 26 (Box 1)
  - 444-Balint Szombathy, 1991 June 6 (Box 1)
  - 445-Frank Kolodny, 1986 October 27 (Box 1)
  - 446-Julien Blaine, 1986 October 13 (Box 1)
  - 447-Pierre Garnier, 1997 December 6 (Box 1)
  - 448-Eric Andersen, undated (Box 1)
  - 449-John Furnival, 2007 January 3 (Box 1)
  - 450-Arrigo Loraa-Totino, 2006 December 13 (Box 1)
  - 451-Luc Fierens, 2007 January 29 (Box 1)
  - 452-Takahashi Shohachiro, 2007 March 1 (Box 1)
  - 453-Pierre Garnier, 2006 December 11 (Box 1)
  - 454-Ito Motoyuki, undated (Box 1)
  - 455-BAU, 2007 April 6 (Box 1)
  - 456-BAU, 2007 March 28 (Box 1)
  - 457-Leonardo Rosa, undated (Box 1)
  - 458-Bern Porter, undated (Box 1)
  - 459-Leonardo Rosa, 1996 June 18 (Box 1)
  - 460-Anna Oberto, 1996 May 30 (Box 1)
  - 461-Pavel Rudolf, 1996 June 18 (Box 1)
  - 462-Jokin Diez, 1997 January 12 (Box 1)